kinkly.com 2019-11-30

# Privacy Policy - Kinkly.com

Kinkly.COM IS COMMITTED TO YOUR PRIVACY. TO LEARN MORE ABOUT THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND USE, THE SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION AND HOW AND WHEN WE SHARE IT, PLEASE READ THE PRIVACY POLICY BELOW. PLEASE READ THIS DOCUMENT CAREFULLY, AS IT GOVERNS YOUR USE OF THE SITE AND ALL SERVICES OFFERED THROUGH THE SITE. 

This policy covers how Kinkly.com treats personal information that we collect and receive, including information related to your past use of our products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable such as your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

Notice to EU Individuals: this Privacy Statement and its enumerated policies are intended to comply with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 (the “General Data Protection Regulation” or “GDPR”) and provide appropriate protection and care with respect to the treatment of your user information in accordance with the GDPR. 

## Information Collection and Use

Kinkly.com collects personal information when you register with Kinkly.com, when you use the site and services offered on the site, when you visit pages on the site or the pages of certain partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Kinkly.com may also combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

Kinkly.com uses such information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. When you register we may ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, postal code and company demographics of the company you work for. When you register with Kinkly.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

Kinkly.com collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of the products and services that we offer. Kinkly.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Kinkly.com cookie information, and the pages you request. 

## Information Sharing & Disclosure

Kinkly.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you request, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of Kinkly.com under confidentiality agreements to provide services in support of the site. These companies may use your personal information to help Kinkly.com communicate with you about offers from Kinkly.com. However, these companies do not have any independent right to use or share this information. We may sometimes share aggregate non-personal information with third parties about how our users utilize the site and services. This aggregate information is typically in the form of statistics, such as numbers of Kinkly.com users who live in a particular locale or fall within a particular age group. Such aggregate information is gathered from individual Kinkly.com users' information but is not traceable to any specific identifiable Kinkly.com user. Kinkly.com may share personal information with third parties to the extent required to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. Kinkly.com may also share personal information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Kinkly.com Terms of Service, or as otherwise required or permitted by law. 

If Kinkly.com is acquired by or merged with or into another company, we will provide public notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. 

## Use of Personal Information with Tell-A-Friend Features

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Kinkly.com does not store this information. It is used for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

## Use of Personal Information with Marketing Partners and Co-Registration

In instances where Kinkly.com and a marketing partner are offering a special value (i.e., a free offering) to our users, we may share your personal information with such partners By signing up to receive items through these promotions, you are expressly consenting to Kinkly.com sharing your personal information (“co-registration”) with such partners and you will become subject to their privacy policies, which may vary from those of Kinkly.com. In the event that you would like to opt-out of receiving offers from these partners, you must do so directly with them. If you have any problems contacting one of our partners, contact us and we will help you resolve the situation. 

In addition, you are expressly consenting to Kinkly.com that the use of certain personally identifiable User data may be processed and shared between applicable third party social network and/or identity providers. User accounts with such third party Providers shall be subject to such third party Providers' then-current terms of use and privacy policies ("Third Party Policies") and Kinkly.com shall not be responsible for any violation of their Policies. You are allowing Kinkly.com to user and store certain of this user data for its own business purposes. 

## Newsletters and Alerts

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s) or alert system, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter or alert to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter, alerts and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by contacting us. We also offer an opportunity to opt-out of certain communications on your _Edit Profile_ page 

## Use of Personal Information Posted on Forums

If you use a forum on this Website, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

## Cookies

Kinkly.com, like many websites, uses cookies. A cookie is a file containing a string of code text that we transfer to your computer's hard drive, to be kept there for later use. With cookies in place, whenever you use your Web browser (such as Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox) to connect to Kinkly.com, our systems are able to recognize you. This enables Kinkly.com to present you with custom web pages and options. For example, instead of seeing a generic welcome page, you might see a welcome page with your site username on it and information about products or services that reflect your interests. 

You can set up your browser to reject cookies or tell you when a cookie has been sent. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of Kinkly.com features and are required for the use of the Site. We hope you will leave them turned on. 

In addition to our cookies, Kinkly.com may allow third parties that show advertisements on our site or participate in co-registration to set and access their own cookies on your computer. The cookies inserted by those third parties are not covered by Kinkly.com Privacy Policy, but rather by the policies of those third parties. However, these third parties do not have access to Kinkly.com cookies. 

Cookies fall into the subcategories below.   
Essential Cookies. Certain cookies are used for specific purposes that are essential to your secure use and navigation of the Site. Without them, Kinkly may not be able to provide core Site functions and features to you, and the Site would not operate as well as you or Kinkly would like. These cookies collect and use information such as your server preferences, single-session data and corresponding identifier, web beacons and log files (detailed below), and other credential-related information. For EU individuals, essential cookies also help inform Kinkly whether you require, or have already been served, an affirmative consent request in connection with the GDPR. Essential cookies include analytics cookies, which provide us data that allows Kinkly to better understand its users and improve the Site based on what we have learned from that data.   
Preference Cookies. Other cookies are used to collect and process information about your preferences and similar choices in connection with the Site in order to optimize your browsing experience (e.g., various local preference settings; which geographically-customized version of the Site and related content you may prefer. Preference cookies include social media cookies, which collect information about your social media usage and other data you may have provided in connection with such usage (if you access the Site through a social media website or mobile application, you may have social media cookies). If you wish to modify or change your social media cookies, please visit and review the settings on your applicable social media account(s).   
Advertising Cookies. To help support the Site and further tailor your experience, Kinkly and its advertising partners (and/or their third party analytics providers) also use cookies on the Site to personalize the content and advertisements you may be shown. Such advertisements use cookies to provide you targeted advertisements that may be more consistent with your interests than non-targeted advertisements. Certain Kinkly advertising partners may also use cookies to monitor or track the performance of their advertising content. Kinkly does not provide user information to advertising partners except in connection with the Site or as required by law.   
If you would like to manage your cookie preferences or learn more information about this practice and your right to decline (or opt-out of) cookies placed by some or all of these companies, you can do so on the GDPR consent notification upon initial site visit.   
We encourage you to consider keeping your cookies enabled, as if you choose to disable the receipt of cookies from our Site, you may not be able to use or benefit from certain features of the Site, particularly the features that are designed to personalize your experience. To learn more about the use of cookies in online advertising including how to manage or delete them [click here](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/).   
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but generally allow users to modify their browser settings to display a warning before accepting a cookie, to accept cookies only from certain websites, and/or to refuse all cookies. 

Kinkly.com also uses Web beacons (also known as action tags or single pixel gifs) to allow us to count how many people have visited a certain page. This enables us to assess the popularity and effectiveness of the material posted on the Kinkly.com website. Additionally, we sometimes use Web beacons to access Kinkly.com cookies inside and outside our Web pages and in connection with Kinkly.com products and services. A Web beacon is a transparent image placed on a Web page that sends a signal when a person visits that page. This enables us to assess the popularity and effectiveness of the material posted on the Kinkly.com website. We may also use Web beacons in connection with emails sent to Kinkly.com users to let us know whether and when the email was opened. 

We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

## Third-Party Ad Serving

We send to your Web browser many of the advertisements you see when you use our network of websites. However, we also allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within our Web pages. Because your Web browser must request these advertising banners from the ad network Website, these companies can send their own cookies to your cookie file, just as if you had requested a Web page from the site. Please note that if an advertiser asks us to show an advertisement to a certain audience or audience segment and you respond to that ad, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience it is trying to reach. As always remember, we only authorize our third-party ad servers to employ anonymous cookies for ad delivery and anonymous targeting. Our third-party ad servers do not collect, nor do we give them access, to any personally identifying information about you. 

We also use third-party ad servers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to Kinkly.com, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other Web sites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a Web beacon or pixel tag, which is industry standard technology, used by most major websites. 

## Opting Out of Third-Party Ad Servers

If you want to prevent a third-party ad server from sending and reading cookies on your computer, you must visit each ad network's website individually and opt out. 

## Editing and/or Deleting Account Information and Preferences

You can edit the information contained in your account at any time by clicking on MY ACCOUNT after logging on to Kinkly.com. You can delete your Kinkly.com account by visiting the ACCOUNT SETTINGS page within your account. Although you account will be deactivated immediately, information provided to us while you were a registered user may remain in back-up storage on our servers indefinitely. Nevertheless, once you delete your account, this information will be inaccessible to the public. 

## Confidentiality and Security

Kinkly.com limits access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably needs such information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. In addition, Kinkly.com maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

Although Kinkly.com takes your privacy seriously and will take reasonable and customary measures to protect it, we cannot guarantee that there will be no unauthorized use of your personal information. 

If you register for the site and services and create a User Account, you will be provided a username and password for such User Account. You acknowledge that you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the password as well as any and all activity that occur under your User Account and password. You agree that at the end of each session using the Site and Services, you will exit your User Account. In the event of any unauthorized use of your password and/or User Account, you agree that you will immediately notify Kinkly.com by sending an email to Kinkly. Kinkly.com cannot and will not be liable for any and all losses or damages arising from your failure to comply with this Section. 

## Third-Party Websites

From time to time, Kinkly.com may make available to you certain services offered by third parties or may include links to sites operated and controlled by third parties. Those third-party services and sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. Users who choose to visit those third-party sites are advised to review their privacy policies. 

## Access to Personal Information

If at any time you would like to review the personal information we collect about you, just ask. You should send an email to Kinkly from the email account you used to create your account and we will provide you with a summary, as well as an opportunity to correct and update this information. 

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be changed from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Kinkly.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. 

## Comments

If you have questions or suggestions, please complete the form on our Contact Us page or write us at: 

Janalta Interactive Inc. o/a Kinkly.com  
1200, 10130 - 103 Street  
Edmonton, Alberta Canada T5J 3N9  
Last updated Friday, November 29, 2019
